## MARLENE KOH

Email: marlenekohxml@gmail.com Mobile: +65 9144 7691

Address: 6 Pandan Valley #19-602 Singapore 597630

## Profile

I am a Year 2 Computer Science Undergraduate Student at National University of Singapore planning to specialize in Software Engineering as well as Computer Graphics and Games.

I am enthusiastic to learn, self-motivated and performance-driven. I enjoy graphic design as a hobby, and I also love to work with colours and vector art.

## Experience

National University of Singapore
----------------------------------

Address Book - Desktop Application ------ Jan 2018 - Present

- Add features to existing 6kLoC base
- Part of CS2103T: Software Engineering
- Written in Java
- Team of 4

Teeny Tiny - PC Game ------ Jan 2018 - Present

- 3D action platformer
- Part of CS3247: Game Development
- Currently at development stage
- Team of 6

BoyfriendBot - Telegram Bot - 28 Jan 2018 - 28 Jan 2018

- Responsive telegram bot that role plays as your boyfriend
- Part of Hack&Roll 2018 (24 hour hackathon)
- Written in Java
- Team of 4

Colour Shift - PC Game ------ 8 Dec 2017 - 9 Dec 2017

- 2D platformer
- Part of GameCraft 2017 (24 hour game jam)
- Written in C#
- Team of 5

Hangry - Android Game ...... May 2017 - August 2017

- 2D side-scroller platformer with gesture detection
- Part of CP2106: Independent Software Development Project (Orbital)
- Written in C#
- Team of 2

Anglo-Chinese Junior College
Spectra (Graphic Design Club)
materials for the school and social organisations
Crescent Girls' School
GCE 'O' Levels Art Coursework 2013
<ul> <li>Created a 5 piece digital artwork which was featured in the SYF 2014 Art Exhibition Showcase</li> </ul>
Work History
Research Assistant under NUS Student Work Scheme (NSWS) Jan 2018 - Present  • Part-time job at the Institute of Water Policy (IWP) at Lee Kuan Yew School of Public Policy (LKYSPP)
Design and create 2D animations for role-playing simulation game project
Teaching Assistant for CS3241 Computer Graphics Jan 2018 - Present  • Conduct and grade biweekly OpenGL programming labs
Education
National University of Singapore 2016 - Present
Bachelor of Computing (Hons) in Computer Science
Anglo-Chinese Junior College 2014 - 2015
GCE 'A' Levels
Crescent Girls' School
GCE 'O' Levels
Skills
<ul> <li>Proficient with Java C C++ C#</li> </ul>

- Basic knowledge of HTML and CSS
- Proficient at Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop
- Proficient at graphic design
- Strong background in 2D animation
- Basic knowledge of 3D animation
- Quick and independent learner
- Detail-oriented, well organized